In this video we will talk
about ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company
and the market capitalization of the company is ₹7946 crore
and the company gives a dividend of 0.3% 70%
and if we talk about the positive point in the company then the
company has reduced its debt and the
company is almost debt free and the
dividend payout of the company is 34.3% and if we
talk about the negative point then
in the last two-three years the promoters' dividend has
reduced by 786 percent
and now let's also see the profit of the company ₹
1049 crore ₹
1194 crore ₹
1473 crore ₹1271 crore ₹
1426 crore
and the promoters' dividend is ₹
480 crore and the secured 25 percent is trading at ₹
1537 and the public dividend is ₹
and at this time the share price is ₹1240
and there is support of ₹1200 and ₹11100 in the share
and at this time this RSS of the picture is coming  I am
in the play zone and this hair had
gone up to sixteen hundred and fifty rupees, currently it is
available at a discount, if you want to buy in this company
then you can start buying them for 12 ₹100
and
if there is a slight fall in the share
then you can add some quantity at the lower level, that's all
in this video, if you
liked the information given in the video then
like the video, share it and
subscribe to our channel dd dd